<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>插件和集成 on Open Cluster Management</title>
    <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 插件和集成 on Open Cluster Management</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Application lifecycle management</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/app-lifecycle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/app-lifecycle/</guid>
      <description>After the cluster manager is installed, you could install the application management components to the hub cluster.
   Architecture Prerequisite Install via Clusteradm CLI tool Install from source What is next     Architecture  For more details, visit the multicloud-operators-subscription GitHub page.
Prerequisite You must meet the following prerequisites to install the application lifecycle management add-on:
  Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.
  Ensure the open-cluster-management cluster manager is installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>多集群网络隧道</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/cluster-proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/cluster-proxy/</guid>
      <description>Cluster proxy is an OCM addon providing L4 network connectivity from hub cluster to the managed clusters without any additional requirement to the managed cluster&amp;rsquo;s network infrastructure by leveraging the Kubernetes official SIG sub-project apiserver-network-proxy.
   Background  About apiserver-network-proxy   Architecture Prerequisite Installation Usage  Command-line tools Example code   More insight  Troubleshooting Related materials       Background The original architecture of OCM allows a cluster from anywhere to be registered and managed by OCM&amp;rsquo;s control plane (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>托管多集群ServiceAccount</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/managed-serviceaccount/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/managed-serviceaccount/</guid>
      <description>Background Prerequisite Installation Usage Related materials     Managed Service Account is an OCM addon enabling a hub cluster admin to manage service account across multiple clusters on ease. By controlling the creation and removal of the service account, the addon agent will project and rotate the corresponding token back to the hub cluster which is very useful for the Kube API client from the hub cluster to request against the managed clusters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policy framework</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/policy-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/policy-framework/</guid>
      <description>The policy framework provides governance capability to gain visibility, and drive remediation for various security and configuration aspects to help IT administrators meet their requirements.
   Architecture Prerequisite Install from prebuilt images on Quay.io What is next     Architecture  You can find the analysis of the architectural components here   Prerequisite You must meet the following prerequisites to install the policy framework:
  Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policy controllers</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/policy-controllers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/zh/getting-started/integration/policy-controllers/</guid>
      <description>After policy framework is installed, you can install the policy controllers to the managed clusters.
   Prerequisite Install the configuration policy controller What is next  Placement Rule API Placement API Final steps to apply the policy   More policies     Prerequisite You must meet the following prerequisites to install the policy controllers:
  Ensure kubectl and kustomize are installed.
  Ensure Golang is installed, if you are planning to install from the source.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>