<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work Distribution on Open Cluster Management</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/work-distribution/</link><description>Recent content in Work Distribution on Open Cluster Management</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/work-distribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ManifestWork</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/work-distribution/manifestwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/work-distribution/manifestwork/</guid><description>What is ManifestWork ManifestWork is used to define a group of Kubernetes resources on the hub to be applied to the managed cluster. In the open-cluster-management project, a ManifestWork resource must be created in the cluster namespace. A work agent implemented in work project is run on the managed cluster and monitors the ManifestWork resource in the cluster namespace on the hub cluster.
An example of ManifestWork to deploy a deployment to the managed cluster is shown in the following example.</description></item><item><title>ManifestWorkReplicaSet</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/work-distribution/manifestworkreplicaset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/work-distribution/manifestworkreplicaset/</guid><description>What is ManifestWorkReplicaSet ManifestWorkReplicaSet is an aggregator API that uses Manifestwork and Placement to create manifestwork for the placement-selected clusters.
View an example of ManifestWorkReplicaSet to deploy a CronJob and Namespace for a group of clusters selected by placements.
apiVersion: work.open-cluster-management.io/v1alpha1 kind: ManifestWorkReplicaSet metadata: name: mwrset-cronjob namespace: ocm-ns spec: placementRefs: - name: placement-rollout-all # Name of a created Placement rolloutStrategy: rolloutType: All - name: placement-rollout-progressive # Name of a created Placement rolloutStrategy: rolloutType: Progressive progressive: minSuccessTime: 5m progressDeadline: 10m maxFailures: 5% mandatoryDecisionGroups: - groupName: &amp;#34;prod-canary-west&amp;#34; - groupName: &amp;#34;prod-canary-east&amp;#34; - name: placement-rollout-progressive-per-group # Name of a created Placement rolloutStrategy: rolloutType: ProgressivePerGroup progressivePerGroup: progressDeadline: 10m maxFailures: 2 manifestWorkTemplate: deleteOption: propagationPolicy: SelectivelyOrphan selectivelyOrphans: orphaningRules: - group: &amp;#39;&amp;#39; name: ocm-ns namespace: &amp;#39;&amp;#39; resource: Namespace manifestConfigs: - feedbackRules: - jsonPaths: - name: lastScheduleTime path: .</description></item></channel></rss>