<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concepts on Open Cluster Management</title>
    <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concepts on Open Cluster Management</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/architecture/</guid>
      <description>This page is an overview of open cluster management.
   Overview  &amp;ldquo;Hub-spoke&amp;rdquo; architecture Modularity and extensibility   Concepts  Cluster registering: &amp;ldquo;double opt-in handshaking&amp;rdquo; Cluster registration security model Cluster namespace Addons   Building blocks  Registration Work Placement Application lifecycle Governance and risk Registration operator       Overview Open Cluster Management (OCM) is a powerful, modular, extensible platform for Kubernetes multi-cluster orchestration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClusterClaim</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/clusterclaim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/clusterclaim/</guid>
      <description>What is ClusterClaim? Usage Example     What is ClusterClaim? ClusterClaim is a cluster-scoped API available to users on a managed cluster. The ClusterClaim objects are collected from the managed cluster and saved into the status of the corresponding ManagedCluster object on the hub.
Usage ClusterCaim is used to specify additional properties of the managed cluster like the clusterID, version, vendor and cloud provider. We defined some reserved ClusterClaims like id.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManagedCluster</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedcluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedcluster/</guid>
      <description>What is ManagedCluster?  Cluster registration and acceptance  Bootstrapping registration Approving registration   Cluster heartbeats and status Cluster taints and tolerations  Taints of ManagedClusters Tolerations of Placements   Cluster removal  Unregister from hub cluster Unregister from the managed cluster     Managed Cluster&amp;rsquo;s certificate rotation What&amp;rsquo;s next?     What is ManagedCluster? ManagedCluster is a cluster scoped API in the hub cluster representing the registered or pending-for-acceptance Kubernetes clusters in OCM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManagedClusterSet</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedclusterset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedclusterset/</guid>
      <description>What is ManagedClusterSet? Operates ManagedClusterSet using clusteradm  Creating a ManagedClusterSet Adding a ManagedCluster to a ManagedClusterSet Binding the ManagedClusterSet to a workspace namespace   A glance at the &amp;ldquo;ManagedClusterSet&amp;rdquo; API  Clusterset RBAC permission control  Adding member cluster to a clusterset Binding a clusterset to a namespace     Default ManagedClusterSet Global ManagedClusterSet     API-CHANGE NOTE:
The ManagedClusterSet and ManagedClusterSetBinding API v1alpha1 version will no longer be served in OCM v0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManifestWork</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/manifestwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/manifestwork/</guid>
      <description>What is ManifestWork Status tracking  Fine-grained field values tracking   Garbage collection  Delete options   Resource Race and Adoption     What is ManifestWork ManifestWork is used to define a group of Kubernetes resources on the hub to be applied to the managed cluster. In the open-cluster-management project, a ManifestWork resource must be created in the cluster namespace. A work agent implemented in work project is run on the managed cluster and monitors the ManifestWork resource in the cluster namespace on the hub cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placement</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/placement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/placement/</guid>
      <description>Overall Select clusters in ManagedClusterSet  Predicates  Label/Claim selection Taints/Tolerations   Prioritizers  Score-based prioritizer Extensible scheduling     PlacementDecisions Troubleshooting  Check the Placement conditions Check the Placement events   Future work     API-CHANGE NOTE: The Placement and PlacementDecision API v1alpha1 version will no longer be served in in OCM v0.9.0.
 Migrate manifests and API clients to use the Placement and PlacementDecision API v1beta1 version, available since OCM v0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add-ons</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/addon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/addon/</guid>
      <description>What is an add-on? Open-cluster-management has a built-in mechanism named addon-framework to help developers to develop an extension based on the foundation components for the purpose of working with multiple clusters in custom cases. A typical addon should consist of two kinds of components:
  Addon Agent: A kubernetes controller in the managed cluster that manages the managed cluster for the hub admins. A typical addon agent is expected to be working by subscribing the prescriptions (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policy</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/policy/</guid>
      <description>Overview Policy PlacementBinding PolicySet Policy Templates  Hub cluster templates Template encryption details Template functions       Overview The policy framework has the following API concepts:
 Policy Templates are the policies that perform a desired check or action. For example, ConfigurationPolicy objects are embedded in Policy objects under the policy-templates array. These cannot be deployed to managed clusters on their own. A Policy is a grouping mechanism for Policy Templates and is the smallest deployable unit on the hub cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>