<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concepts on Open Cluster Management</title>
    <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concepts on Open Cluster Management</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/architecture/</guid>
      <description>This page is an overview of open cluster management.
   Overview  &amp;ldquo;Hub-spoke&amp;rdquo; architecture Modularity and extensibility   Concepts  Cluster registering: &amp;ldquo;double opt-in handshaking&amp;rdquo; Cluster namespace Addons   Building blocks  Registration Work Placement Application lifecycle Governance and risk Registration operator       Overview Open Cluster Management (OCM) is a powerful, modular, extensible platform for Kubernetes multi-cluster orchestration. Learning from the past failing lesson of building Kubernetes federation systems in the Kuberentes community, in OCM we will be jumping out of the legacy centric, imperative architecture of Kubefed v2 and embracing the &amp;ldquo;hub-agent&amp;rdquo; architecture which is identical to the original pattern of &amp;ldquo;hub-kubelet&amp;rdquo; from Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManagedCluster</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedcluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedcluster/</guid>
      <description>What is ManagedCluster?  Cluster registration and acceptance  Bootstrapping registration Approving registration   Cluster heartbeats and status Cluster taints and tolerations  Taints of ManagedClusters Tolerations of Placements   Cluster removal  Unregister from hub cluster Unregister from the managed cluster     ManagedClusterSet     What is ManagedCluster? ManagedCluster is a cluster scoped API in the hub cluster representing the registered or pending-for-acceptance Kubernetes clusters in OCM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManagedClusterSet</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedclusterset/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/managedclusterset/</guid>
      <description>What is ManagedClusterSet? Operates ManagedClusterSet using clusteradm  Creating a ManagedClusterSet Adding a ManagedCluster to a ManagedClusterSet Bind the clusterset to a workspace namespace   A glance at the &amp;ldquo;ManagedClusterSet&amp;rdquo; API  Clusterset RBAC permission control  Adding member cluster to a clusterset Binding a clusterset to a namespace     Default ManagedClusterSet     What is ManagedClusterSet? ManagedClusterSet is a cluster scoped API in the hub cluster for grouping a few managed clusters into a &amp;ldquo;set&amp;rdquo; so that hub admin can operate these clusters altogether in a higher level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ManifestWork</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/manifestwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/manifestwork/</guid>
      <description>What is ManifestWork Status tracking  Fine-grained field values tracking   Garbage collection  Delete options   Resource Race and Adoption     What is ManifestWork ManifestWork is used to define a group of Kubernetes resources on the hub to be applied to the managed cluster. In the open-cluster-management project, a ManifestWork resource must be created in the cluster namespace. A work agent implemented in work project is run on the managed cluster and monitors the ManifestWork resource in the cluster namespace on the hub cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placement</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/placement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/placement/</guid>
      <description>Overall Select clusters in ManagedClusterSet  Predicates  Label/Claim selection Taints/Tolerations   Prioritizers  Score-based prioritizer     Extensible scheduling Future work     API-CHANGE NOTE: Placement and PlacementDecision API is upgraded from v1alpha1 to v1beta1, v1alpha1 will be deprecated in OCM v0.7.0 and planned to be removed in OCM v0.8.0. The field spec.prioritizerPolicy.configurations.name in Placement API v1alpha1 is removed and replaced by spec.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add-ons</title>
      <link>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/addon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://open-cluster-management.io/concepts/addon/</guid>
      <description>What is an add-on? Open-cluster-management has a built-in mechanism named addon-framework to help developers to develop an extension based on the foundation components for the purpose of working with multiple clusters in custom cases. A typical addon should consist of two kinds of components:
  Addon Agent: A kubernetes controller in the managed cluster that manages the managed cluster for the hub admins. A typical addon agent is expected to be working by subscribing the prescriptions (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>