<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cluster Inventory on Open Cluster Management</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/</link><description>Recent content in Cluster Inventory on Open Cluster Management</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ClusterClaim</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/clusterclaim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/clusterclaim/</guid><description>What is ClusterClaim? ClusterClaim is a cluster-scoped API available to users on a managed cluster. The ClusterClaim objects are collected from the managed cluster and saved into the status of the corresponding ManagedCluster object on the hub.
Usage ClusterCaim is used to specify additional properties of the managed cluster like the clusterID, version, vendor and cloud provider. We defined some reserved ClusterClaims like id.k8s.io which is a unique identifier for the managed cluster.</description></item><item><title>ManagedCluster</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/managedcluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/managedcluster/</guid><description>What is ManagedCluster? ManagedCluster is a cluster scoped API in the hub cluster representing the registered or pending-for-acceptance Kubernetes clusters in OCM. The klusterlet agent working in the managed cluster is expected to actively maintain/refresh the status of the corresponding ManagedCluster resource on the hub cluster. On the other hand, removing the ManagedCluster from the hub cluster indicates the cluster is denied/exiled from the hub cluster. The following is the introduction of how the cluster registration lifecycle works under the hood:</description></item><item><title>ManagedClusterSet</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/managedclusterset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/concepts/cluster-inventory/managedclusterset/</guid><description>API-CHANGE NOTE:
The ManagedClusterSet and ManagedClusterSetBinding API v1beta1 version will no longer be served in OCM v0.12.0.
Migrate manifests and API clients to use the ManagedClusterSet and ManagedClusterSetBinding API v1beta2 version, available since OCM v0.9.0. All existing persisted objects are accessible via the new API. Notable changes: The default cluster selector type will be ExclusiveClusterSetLabel in v1beta2, and type LegacyClusterSetLabel in v1beta1 is removed. What is ManagedClusterSet? ManagedClusterSet is a cluster-scoped API in the hub cluster for grouping a few managed clusters into a &amp;ldquo;set&amp;rdquo; so that hub admin can operate these clusters altogether in a higher level.</description></item></channel></rss>