<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Administration on Open Cluster Management</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/getting-started/administration/</link><description>Recent content in Administration on Open Cluster Management</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/getting-started/administration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monitoring OCM using Prometheus-Operator</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/getting-started/administration/monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/getting-started/administration/monitoring/</guid><description>In this page, we provide a way to monitor your OCM environment using Prometheus-Operator.
Before you get started You must have a OCM environment setuped. You can also follow our recommended quick start guide to set up a playgroud OCM environment.
And then please install the Prometheus-Operator in your hub cluster. You can also run the following commands copied from the official doc:
git clone https://github.com/prometheus-operator/kube-prometheus.git cd kube-prometheus # Create the namespace and CRDs, and then wait for them to be availble before creating the remaining resources kubectl create -f manifests/setup # Wait until the &amp;#34;servicemonitors&amp;#34; CRD is created.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading your OCM environment</title><link>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/getting-started/administration/upgrading/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://open-cluster-management.io/docs/getting-started/administration/upgrading/</guid><description>This page provides the suggested steps to upgrade your OCM environment including both the hub cluster and the managed clusters. Overall the major steps you should follow are:
Read the release notes to confirm the latest OCM release version. (Note that some add-ons&amp;rsquo; version might be different from OCM&amp;rsquo;s overall release version.) Upgrade your command line tools clusteradm Before you begin You must have an existing OCM environment and there&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be registration-operator running in your clusters.</description></item></channel></rss>